wizehive.com 2014-12-19

# WizeHive - Enterprise Collaboration, Business Process and Workflow

Your privacy is important to WizeHive, Inc. ("WizeHive", "we", "us" or "our"). This privacy policy provides details about how your personal information is collected and used by us. Personal information is any information that identifies you or would enable someone to contact you, such as your name, email address, phone number and other non-public information associated with your individual identity. This privacy policy explains our commitment to protecting the privacy of personal information about users of WizeHive websites, software, products and services (collectively, the "Site"). We reserve the right to change this Policy from time to time and will notify you of any changes via email or on our web site.

##### Information Collected

We may collect personal information when you register to use the Site. Personal information may include your name, username, your password (we only store an encrypted version of this; not the actual password), one or more email addresses and other contact information. For paying customers we may ask for additional information such as credit card number, billing address and related information.

Like most web-based services, we may automatically collect information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personal information or the WizeHive user ID.

Like many websites, we may also use "cookies" to collect information. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. We may use "persistent cookies" to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site; and we may use "session ID cookies" to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Site. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of our services.

##### Our Use of Information

We use the information collected to enable your access to and use of the Site, to personalize the Site for you, or to supply you services that you have asked for. If you are a paying customer we will also use this information to charge your credit card or collect payments from you.

We may also occasionally contact you via email to tell you about web maintenance, upgrades and new features regarding our promotions or those on behalf of third parties, but will provide you with a vehicle for opting out of these emails.

We do not sell, rent or share customer personal information with third parties. We do not sell customer lists to marketers.

We may contact you by email regarding your orders and our services. You may elect not to receive commercial marketing messages from us about the services.

We do not store any credit card numbers in our system except to process and transmit the information for payment processing. If you enter your credit card information to place an order, that information is encrypted and transmitted immediately for processing and authorization. Once the transaction is authorized, we delete the credit card information from our system. If the services you purchase require recurring billing, your information is encrypted and maintained by our payment processing provider.

We may assign you a user ID and password to use the Site. We assume no responsibility for preventing third parties (other than our own employees) from using your login credentials, whether with or without your permission.

##### Customer Use of Information

As a user of the Site, you may be permitted to enter personal information to apply for and/or participate in certain programs or projects conducted by our customers using the Site. Such programs or projects may include, without limitation, contests, scholarships, grants and business communications and transactions. When you use the Site for these purposes, we may collect, store and forward your name, email address and other personal information to the customer sponsoring or conducting each such program or project. Each of our customers is responsible for any further use of your personal information as well as operation of each program and project. Use of your personal information by a customer may be governed by rules and/or privacy policies established independently by the customer as well as laws and regulations applicable to the customer. We assume no responsibility for any customer's use of any personal information you submit through the Site for the purpose of applying for or participating in any customer program or project.

##### User and Customer Lists

Our customer and user list is an asset and trade secret of WizeHive, Inc. and may be transferred with the company's assets in connection with any merger, acquisition or change of control of the business of the company. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

##### Required Disclosures

Except as stated in this privacy policy, we will not disclose your personal information to third parties except when we must comply with laws that require such disclosure to law enforcement authorities or other government third party officials such as subpoenas.

If we are required by law, regulation or legal process (e.g. subpoena) to disclose information about you, we will notify you to the extent permitted by law but we reserve the right to disclose such information as legally required in our judgment. We also may disclose information about your use of the Site if we have reason to believe you have used the Site for purposes prohibited in our [Terms of Service](http://www.wizehive.com/terms_of_service/) or that it is necessary to avoid injury, damage to property or violation of someone's rights.

##### Updating Personal Information

If your personal information changes, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove information through the Site or by emailing our Customer Support team at [support@wizehive.com](mailto:support@wizehive.com). We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

##### Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card information) on your online registration we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our site, you can email us at [support@wizehive.com](mailto:support@wizehive.com). 

##### Other Websites & Links

The Site may contain links to other websites or services maintained by our customers or third parties. We make no representation or warranties and are not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

##### Children

Our site is designed to be used by people over 13 years of age. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA") protects the online privacy of children under 13 years of age. WizeHive does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from anyone under the age of 13, unless or except as permitted by law. Any person who provides Personal Information through our site represents to us that he or she is 13 years of age or older. If we learn that Personal Information has been collected from a user under 13 years of age, then we will take the appropriate steps to cause this information to be deleted.

For more information, contact us at 1-877-767-9493

Updated January 2014
